# Yuri Gravatá

# Full-stack WebDeveloper

27 years old

yuri@gravata.dev - +55 21 98170-8481 - Rio de Janeiro - Brasil



## PERSONAL PROFILE

With 7 years of business background, bilingual and fast-learner, I'm a Le Wagon's coding bootcamp graduate looking for a full-time position in an inovative company, with a strong tech culture, where I'll solve problems, generate positive business impact and will deepen my programming skills and knowledge.

# WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

#### repLAI: www.replai.org

- · A website that allows and facilitates the request for access to public data at different levels of Rio de Janeiro government;
- And it's a repository of public data, fostering collaboration from society to society;
- Built in with: JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Ajax, HTML5, CSS/Sass, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap also working remotely as a team using Github, Heroku and Slack;

#### **GREENSTORE:** greenstore354.herokuapp.com

- A cannabis marketplace;
- Built in with: JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Ajax, HTML5, CSS/Sass, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap also working remotely as a team using Github, Heroku and Slack;

# Gravatá's Cocktail: https://gravata-cocktails.herokuapp.com/

- A cocktail recipe site to add, edit and display drinks;
- Built in with: JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS/Sass, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, MVC Architecture, using Github, Heroku;

**Profile Page:** ygravata.github.io/profile/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Cambará - Exchange Manager

06/2016 - Present

- Analysis and approval of exchange operations;
- Passive / active business relationship;
- Maintenance of the customer base and after-sales relationship:

# Frottas (Project) - Financial Coordinator

04/2018 - 09/2018

- · Implementation of financial management and control system;
- · Identification of the company's debt and achievement of the established target of a reduction of 30% of expenses;

# **Delfiori** - Sales Coordinator

09/2015 - 05/2016

- · Developing, implementation and analysis of processes to track sales results;
- Management of 6 store managers;
- Reformulation of inventory processes and stores sales sector:

#### **EDUCATION**

## **LeWagon:** Coding Bootcamp

**Full-Stack Web Developer** January 2020 - June 2020

#### PUC - Rio

**Bachelor of Business** August 2011 - July 2015

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Ruby on Rails;
- · APIs, JSON, scraping;
- Relational databases, SQL, Postgres;
- HTML, CSS/Sass, Bootstrap;
- ES6 Javascript, Ajax;
- · Wireframes, prototyping, UI Design;
- OOP
- MVC Architecture;
- · Test Driven Development;
- Git, Github, Technical workflow;

#### **LANGUAGE - FLUENT**

**English** 

**Portuguese**